ABULA MARTINS ONYEMUCHE

abulamartins@gmail.com

phone number: +2347065912821 Website: https://mdmuche.vercel.app Address: Port Harcourt, Rivers State

Profile:

I am a Front-End Web Developer with 1 year experience in Html, Css, Javascript And React. I also have knowledge of some backend frameworks such as Node.js, Express and MongoDB. I have built projects which you can access via my github profile: https://www.github.com/mdmuche

Experience:

whitecreativity (intern): Period (April 2018 – September 2018)

- understanding and implementation of html, css to build simple website
- built web pages from the front end using sublime text

Nysc: Period (March 2021–february 2022)

Community Secondary School Aka Offot/Mathematics Teacher:

- Prepared lesson notes and plan
- Administered standardised test to evaluate student progress
- Recorded students assignment and test scores on my grade book to monitor progress

Ad'mas Digital Technologies (intern): Period (October 2022 - November 2022)

- Learnt the basics of html and css with vscode editor
- Learnt the basics of javascript

Elitepath Software (intern): Period (December 2022 - january 2023)

- Was introduced to React js by building a blog
- Learnt Nodejs, Express and mongoDB by building an ecommerce website using the mvc

Education:

Certificates:

2000-2006	provil nursery	and primar	y school ((First School	Leaving Certificate)

2006–2012 immaculate comprehensive college (WAEC)

2016–2019 Rivers State University (BSc)

2022 Ad'mas digital technologies limited (Basic Web Development)

Languages:

- ogba (Mother Tongue)
- English

Personal Details:

Date of Birth : 18-08-1996

Gender : Male

Marital Status : Single

Name : Abula Martins Onyemuche

Contact Address : Onelga, Rivers State Nigeria

Nationality : Nigerian

Declaration

I hereby declare that the above particulars are true to the best of my knowledge and I here by bear the responsibility for the correctness of the above mentioned particulars.

Skills:

- Html
- Css
- Javascript
- React
- Bootstrap

PROJECTS:

Blog project using React js

https://github.com/mdmuche/myblogapp

ecommerce project using React, Nodejs, Express, and mongoDb

https://github.com/mdmuche/elitepath cohort 2023 jan

A final Ecommerce project using React, Nodejs, Express, and mongoDb

https://github.com/mdmuche/elitepath behance final ecommerce project

A Movie Discovery Website using React, and tmdb api to fetch data

https://hmovies-ruby.vercel.app

COMMUNICATIONS

Building professional relationships

Fluent in English

HOBBIES

Reading, Writing, Jugging & Travelling.

REFEREES:

Available on request